{
    "id": "6d8cf2cca25e4d3694aef9a6f0aa0610",
    "title": "Adjective Or Adverb",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "If you work too …………………………………., you will fall ill.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "hard",
                "hardly"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "3d42822dd63c4061aea4eb5bb882e081"
        },
        {
            "question": "The country received …………………………………… any rainfall this year.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "hard",
                "hardly"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "e6cc37b147da415abaa5b03ea94b0114"
        },
        {
            "question": "In a democratic country, everybody has the right to speak …………………………….",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "free",
                "freely"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "c9f2c1bcc5f44a7380d2294f32d446f5"
        },
        {
            "question": "He hit the nail ................................................",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "hard",
                "hardly"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "e918fef4cc244504b11d60874f51d42d"
        },
        {
            "question": "The show was ……………………………………… amusing.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "high",
                "highly"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "576f83d1ece942c58e832f27c242e956"
        },
        {
            "question": "Throw it as ………………………………………. as you can.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "high",
                "highly"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "4a466950a806404fa47630e5719f497c"
        },
        {
            "question": "He has ……………………………………. arrived.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "just",
                "justly"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "351eda718dfc4e468721fca5bb30eb59"
        },
        {
            "question": "All criminals must be ……………………………………….. punished for their crimes.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "just",
                "justly"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "b4fb1d9de23b4ae797fe77d0ab6a2d13"
        },
        {
            "question": "He is never ………………………………………… for work.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "late",
                "lately"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "feecc99e70f24c278f87347ee81fc2cb"
        },
        {
            "question": "I haven’t been to the theatre much …………………………………………",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "late",
                "lately"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "3aaa8ecae2d34d518053cbaaadaf3662"
        }
    ]
}